Oh, my God!
어머나!
I know. Monica's gonna have a baby!
모니카가 아일 낳다니
이것도 '새 것 목록'에
넣을 수 있을까?
Can this count as her "something new"?
어쩌면 좋아
Oh, my God.
Do you think
this is why he took off?
이것 때문에 챈들러가
사라진 걸까?
She had to have just taken it.
I took out the trash last night.
어젯밤에 쓰레기 버렸으니
테스트한 지 얼마 안 돼
최악의 결혼식이 되겠군
It's turning into
the worst wedding ever.
신부는 임신했고 신랑은 사라지고
난 아직 이걸 들고 있네
The bride's pregnant, the groom's
missing and I'm holding this.
피비, 아직 아무한테도
얘기하면 안 돼
Phoebe, we cannot tell
anyone about this.
- 그래, 맞아
- 알았지?
-Right. Yeah.
-Okay?
Do you know what kind
of birth control she uses?
잠깐만, 모니카가 쓰던
피임약 뭔지 알아?
No. Why?
아니, 왜?
Just for the future.
This is hardly a commercial for it.
나도 나중에 참고하게
The One With Monica and Chandler's Wedding
Anything?
어떻게 됐어?
No. I talked to Joey.
He hasn't heard from him.
조이한테 전화했는데
아무 소식 못 들었대
챈들러 부모님한테도
전화했고
I talked to Chandler's parents again.
사라졌다고 했어?
-You said he was missing?
-No.
아니, 그냥 안부차
전화한 척 했어
It seemed like I called to chat.
그런데 두분 다 내가
관심있다고 생각하셔
Pretty sure they both think
I'm interested.
- 모니카한테 말해야돼
- 안 돼, 못해
-We've got to tell her.
-No, we can't.
곧 준비할 텐데
She'll start getting ready soon.
어제 갔던데 또 가볼 테니
시간 좀 끌어봐
Can't you stall her? I'll go
to the places I went last night.
얼마나?
How much time?
준비하는 시간 빼고
얼마나 시간이 있어?
How long before she has to get ready?
- 한 시간
- 두 시간 줘
-One hour.
-Give me two.
그럴 거 왜 물어봤어?
Then why do you ask?
- 행운을 빌어줘
- 나도 같이 가
-Wish me luck.
-I'm going with you.
Why?
왜?
You're tired. You looked all night.
And clearly, you suck at this.
너 밤새도록 찾아 다녔는데
별로 소질이 없잖아
나중에 봐
See you later.
어떻게 시간 끌 거야?
Wait, do you know how
you're gonna stall her?
-I'll figure something out.
-Okay, good luck.
- 방법을 찾아야지
- 그래, 잘해
화장부터 하고
머리해야겠다
Let's start with my makeup
and then do my hair.
좋아, 그 전에
얘기 좀 하자
Okay. But before you do that,
I need you to talk to me.
About what?
무슨 얘기?
I'm never gonna get married!
난 평생 결혼 못할 거야!
너도 금방 좋은 남자
만날 거야
You will. The right
guy's around the corner.
Okay, are we done with that?
이제 됐지?
아니, 나 심각해
No, I'm serious.
Maybe I should just forget about it.
Become a lesbian or something.
결혼 같은 거 포기하고
레즈비언이나 될까 봐
너 잡는 여자는 땡잡은 거지
Any woman would be lucky to have you.
조이하고 자고나면
기분이 나아지려나
Maybe I'd feel better
if I slept with Joey.
레이첼? 너 괜찮아?
Rachel? Are you okay?
Excuse me, Aaron? I have
a little problem with the schedule.
감독님? 제 스케줄에
문제가 좀 있어서요
I wasn't supposed to work today.
I have a wedding that I have to be at.
오늘 결혼식이 있어서
일 못하거든요
It's my best friend's,
and I'm officiating...
친한 친구 결혼식인데
제가 주례거든요
...so I really can't work past 4.
4시 전에 끝나야 하는데
끝날 때까지 있어야 하네
중간에 갈 순 없다네
You've gotta stay until the end.
We can't stop filming just for you.
자네 결혼식도 아니잖아
It's not like it's your wedding.
저 수술해요
I'm having surgery.
What?
뭐라고?
걱정할까 봐 결혼식
얘기 지어낸 거예요
I made up the wedding,
because I didn't want you to worry.
But I'm having surgery today.
오늘 수술하거든요
What kind of surgery?
무슨 수술?
이식 수술요
Transplant.
You're supposed to work on Monday.
월요일에 일해야 되잖아
Hair transplant.
머리카락 이식 수술요
대머리도 아닌데
But you're not bald.
It's not on my head.
머리에 말고요
There's nothing I can do.
You'll probably be out by 4 anyway.
어쩔 수 없다네
4시 전엔 끝날 거야
한 장면만 찍으면 되는데
리차드는 프로잖아
We've got one scene. It's just you
and Richard, and he's a pro.
You'll be fine.
괜찮을 걸세
왔나, 리차드
Morning, Richard.
Hey, you're here! Great!
Let's go, buddy!
오셨어요? 잘 됐네요
시작해요
오늘 촬영 있어요!
We got a scene to shoot!
나 벨트 두 개 찼어
I'm wearing two belts.
-Are you drunk?
-No.
- 취하셨어요?
- 아니
취하셨잖아요!
Yes, you are!
그렇다고 해
All right.
여기가 네 사무실이구나
So this is your office?
How'd you guys find me?
I knew I should've hid at the gym.
어떻게 찾았어?
헬스클럽에 숨을 걸
-What the hell are you doing?
-Panicking.
- 도대체 뭐하는 거야?
- 겁먹고 있지
And using the lnternet to try to prove
that I'm related to Monica.
그리고 인터넷에서 모니카와
친척이란 증거를 찾고 있어
-How is she?
-She doesn't know you're gone.
- 모니카 어때?
- 너 사라진 거 몰라
알아서도 안 되지
자, 집에 가자
And she doesn't have to know.
Come on, we're going home.
- 못하겠어
- 왜 못해?
-I can't do that.
-Why not?
집에 가면 모니카와 난
빙 부부가 되는데
If I go home,
we're gonna become the Bings.
I can't be the Bings.
그럴 순 없어
뭐가 어때서?
What's wrong with it?
빙 부부는 결혼생활이
엉망이거든
The Bings have bad marriages.
소리치고, 싸우고
They yell, fight,
and use the pool boy...
수영장 청소부를 내기로
성적 게임을 하거든
...as a pawn in their sexual games.
너 검은 드레스 입고
나 호텔로 부른 적 있어?
Have you ever put on a black dress
and asked me up to your hotel room?
- 아니
- 그럼 넌 네 부모님과 달라
-No.
-Then you are neither of your parents.
그 분들뿐만 아니라
너만 봐도 그래
It's not just their marriage.
Look at yours. Look at everybody's.
성공적인 결혼을 지탱할
사람은 폴 뉴먼 뿐이야
Only Paul Newman
can make marriage work.
나를 아는데
난 폴 뉴먼이 못돼
And I am no Paul Newman.
자동차 경주도 못하지
자선단체에 기부도 안하지
I don't race cars or make popcorn.
None of my proceeds go to charity.
그렇지만, 챈들러
But look, Chandler...
현재 나보다 널 우습게 보는
사람은 없을 거야
...right now no one has
a lower opinion of you than I do.
그런데도 난 네가
해낼 거라고 믿어
But I totally believe you can do this.
해내고 싶어, 모니카를
사랑하지만 너무나...
I want to. I love her so much,
but I'm afraid--
It's too huge.
너무 큰 일이잖아
맞아, 큰 일이지
You're right. It is huge.
그러니 한 번에
한가지씩만 하자
So let's take it
just a little bit at a time.
Forget getting married for a sec.
결혼 따윈 잊어버려
그 생각은 하지 마
그냥 집에 가서
샤워는 할 수 있지?
Can you just come home
and take a shower?
그건 안 무섭지?
That's not scary, right?
Depends on what you mean by "we."
"우리"가 누구냐에
따라 다르지
밤이 더 힘들어
The nights are the hardest.
그러다 낮이 오면
But then the day comes...
낮도 밤만큼 힘들고
...and that's every bit
as hard as the night.
- 그러다 밤이 또 오면...
- 밤낮으로 힘들다, 알았어
-Then the night comes--
-Days and nights are hard, I get it!
준비해야 돼
오늘 결혼식이란 말야
I have to start getting ready.
I'm getting married today.
알아, 해질녘이지
I know. At dusk.
그때가 가장 힘든 때야
That's such a hard time for me.
나 화장해야돼
한 시간 후에 호텔가야 돼
I'm gonna put makeup on.
We have to be there in an hour.
- 잠깐!
- 뭐야?
-Wait!
-What?
점심먹으러 가자
Let's go to lunch!
지금 못 가!
I can't go to lunch!
그렇지
Right.
아이구, 이런, 넘어진다
Oh, good God, I've fallen down.
What's going on?
무슨 일이야?
All right, honey, listen.
좋아, 잘 들어
When I tell you what I'm
about to tell you, remember...
내 말 듣기 전에
잘 기억해두길 바래
...that we're all here for you,
and we love you.
우린 널 사랑하고
널 위해 뭐든 할 거야
좋아, 겁주지 말고
Okay, you're really freaking me out.
We can't find Chandler--
못 찾겠어, 챈들러...
His vest.
조끼를
We can't find Chandler's vest.
챈들러 조끼를 못 찼겠어
뭐야?
잠깐, 그 말 사실이야?
How can that be?
Wait, are you serious?
Found the vest.
조끼 찾았어
다시 안 잃어버리게
잘 감시해야겠어
We'll have to keep an eye on it,
make sure we don't lose it again.
좋아, 그런 식으로
나 겁주지 마
Oh, wow! Okay, don't
scare me like that, okay?
잠깐 동안 최악의 일이
일어난 줄 알았잖아
For a minute, I was like,
"Oh, my God! The worst has happened!"
두 분 결혼 하셨다고요?
So you two were married, huh?
What happened, you just drift apart?
어쩌다 헤어지셨어요?
신부 나옵니다
Here comes the bride.
Oh, my God, Monica!
어머나, 모니카!
I want to wear this every day.
이 거 매일 입고 싶어
You look so beautiful.
정말 예쁘다
I'm so happy for me.
나 좋아 죽겠어
-Hello?
-Did Chandler show up yet?
- 여보세요?
- 챈들러 찾았어?
- 찾았어, 아무 문제없어
- 젠장!
-We got him back. Everything's fine.
-Damn it!
- 왜? 너 어디야?
- 아직 촬영장
-Where are you?
-I'm still on the set.
The wedding is in less than an hour.
결혼식 한 시간도 안 남았어
알아, 상대역이 취했어
끝날때까진 안 보내준대
I'm sorry. The guy's drunk.
They won't let me go until we get it.
맙소사, 다른 주례를
찾아봐야겠다
Oh, my God. I'm gonna
have to find another minister.
안 돼, 내가 주례야
No, I'm the minister!
두 사람 바꿔줘
당장 결혼시키게
Put them both on the phone
and I'll marry them right now.
조이, 그만 끊자
Joey, I have to go.
끊지 마! 안 그럼 당장
너와 결혼해 버릴 거야
Don't hang up on me! I'll marry you
and me right now! I have the power!
There you go! You put on a tuxedo!
거 봐! 턱시도 입었네
겁나지 않았지?
That wasn't scary, was it?
No.
응
내 말대로 한 번에
하나씩 하는 거야
I'm telling you,
just a little bit at a time.
이제 다음은 뭐야?
Okay. What's the next little bit?
Getting married.
결혼하는 거
할 수 있어
지금껏 해온대로만 해
You can do that too.
Just like you've done everything else.
Yeah, you're right. I can do that.
그래, 난 할 수 있어
- 잠깐 나갔다 올게
- 어딜 가?
-Excuse me for a minute.
-Where you going?
도망가는 거 아냐
신선한 공기 좀 마시게
I'm not gonna run away.
I just want some fresh air.
- 좋아
-Okay.
아, 신선한 공기!
Oh, fresh air!
- 나 대신 좀 해줘
- 너 과민반응하는 거 아냐?
-Cover for me.
-Maybe you overreacted. You do that.
방법을 찾아야 돼
We gotta do something.
조이가 못 올지 모르니
다른 결혼식이 있나 볼게
Joey won't make it, so I'll
look around for other weddings.
Don't tell them Monica's pregnant,
because they frown on that.
모니카 임신 얘긴 하지 마
그럼 안하려고 할 걸
알았어
Okay.
아나스타사키스와
파파시파키스라, 좋았어
Anastassakis Papasifakis Wedding.
Excellent.
Congratulations.
축하해요
행운을 빌어요
Hi! Oh, great hat.
모자 멋지네요
I need you to perform another wedding.
Can you do that?
결혼식 주례 하나 더
서 주실 수 있으세요?
글쎄요,
그리스 정교회 신도입니까?
I don't know.
Are they Greek Orthodox?
네, 그럼요
Yeah. Yeah.
제 친구인데
모니카 스테파노폴리스
They're my friends,
Monica Stephanopolis.
And Chandler Acidophilus.
챈들러 아시도필러스예요
안녕하세요
Has anyone seen Chandler?
챈들러 못 보셨어요?
- 너와 같이 있었잖아
- 같이 있었죠
-I thought he was with you.
-He was with me.
We're playing a game. Hide-and-seek.
숨바꼭질 하는 중이거든요
우리한테 물으면 안 되지
반칙이잖아
You can't ask us, son.
That's cheating.
You're right.
Thanks for keeping me honest, Dad.
맞아요,
일깨워 주셔서 고마워요
여긴 안 와야지
신부를 보면 안 되잖아
He can't come here and see
the bride in her wedding dress.
내 기억으론 우리 결혼식 땐
신랑이 드레스를 입었지
When we got married,
I saw the groom in the wedding dress.
결혼 끝난 후니까
나쁜 징크스는 아냐
That was after the wedding.
It's not bad luck then.
좋은 일도 아니지
Honey, it isn't good luck.
와! 모니카
Oh, my God! Monica.
나 예쁘지!
I know!
-How's Chandler doing?
-Great.
- 챈들러는 어때?
- 좋아
잘하고 있어
챈들러 걱정은 하지마
He's doing great.
Don't you worry about Chandler.
- 피비, 나 좀 볼까?
- 그래
-Phoebe, can I see you for a second?
-Yeah.
- 무슨 일이야?
- 챈들러가 또 사라졌어
-What's going on?
-Chandler's gone again.
그러게 그런 애랑
왜 숨바꼭질은 하고 그래?
Why would you play hide-and-seek with
someone you know is a flight risk?
감독님, 보내주세요
리차드 맛이 갔다고요
Aaron, you gotta let me go.
The guy's hammered.
미안하네만 그 친구
정신이 있는 한 촬영은 해
I'm sorry. As long as he's here
and conscious, we're still shooting.
You wouldn't happen to have
a very big fork?
자네 혹 큰 포크
가진 거 없나?
So, I just talked to the director.
감독님과 얘기했는데
오늘 촬영 끝났대요
That's it. We're done for the day.
We finished the scene?
촬영 끝났다고?
- 아주 훌륭하셨어요
- 자네도
-You were wonderful.
-As were you.
So I got your car.
It's right outside.
밖에 차 대기시켰어요
Thank you. You're welcome.
고맙네, 천만에
No, we gotta go. Come on.
Here we go.
가봐야죠, 어서요
이게 내 엉덩인가?
Is that my ass?
-There he is!
-What?
- 저기 있다!
- 뭐가?
You won't get away this time!
이 번엔 절대 못 봐줘!
내가 전에 혼낸다고 했지!
Unless you want
that ass-kicking we talked about!
Ross!
로스!
I'm serious! You're not
walking out on my sister!
진짜야! 내 동생한테
상처주기만 해 봐!
그런 일 없어
That's right. I'm not.
-Then where have you been?
-I know about Monica.
- 어디 갔다 온 거야
- 모니카 일 알아
-You know?
-What?
- 알고 있어?
- 뭘?
너와 레이첼 얘기
들었어
-I heard you and Rachel talking.
-About what?
- 뭐? 무슨 얘기야?
- 넌 몰라?
You don't know?
누가 당장 말하지 않으면
지금...
If somebody doesn't tell me
right now....
또 "하이야"하게?
What, you'll "hi-yah"?
Monica's pregnant.
모니카가 임신했대
Oh, my God.
맙소사
그런데 너 겁 안 먹었어?
Oh, my God.
And you're not freaking out?
먹었지, 그래서
담배 사러 가게에 갔다가...
I was. Then I went to the
gift shop for cigarettes.
- 담배?
- 그게 대수야, 지금?
-Cigarettes?
-Big picture, please!
So I was in the gift shop,
that's when I saw this....
가게에 갔다가
이걸 봤어
And I thought anything that can
fit into this can't be scary.
그래서 이 옷이 맞는다면
겁낼 이유가 없다고 생각했어
You obviously
didn't see Chuckie III.
사탄의 인형 3편을
못봐서 그래
이것 봐, 얼마나 작고 귀여워
But come on, look at how cute
and small this is.
So I got it to give Monica,
so she'd know I was okay.
그래서 모니카에게
내 맘을 알릴려고 샀어
자식
Dude.
Way to go, son.
I knew you'd find him.
잘 했다, 찾을 줄 알았어
우리 아들이 결혼을 하다니
Our little boy is getting married.
정말 핸섬하구나
Look at you, so handsome.
You look beautiful, Mom.
엄마도 아름다우세요
You look beautiful too, Dad.
아버지도 아름답고요
I love you both.
두 분 다 사랑해요
와 주셔서 기뻐요
I'm so glad you're here.
Are you Chandler?
자네가 챈들런가?
조이세요?
Are you Joey?
-This is nice.
-What?
- 좋은데
- 뭐가?
I've never walked down the aisle
knowing it can't end in divorce.
이혼하지 않을 거란 확신으로
여길 걷긴 처음이야
할머니가 살아 계셨음
좋았을 텐데
I wish your grandmother
had lived to see this.
-She's right there.
-Not that old crone. My mother.
- 저기 계시잖아요
- 그 노인네 말고 우리 엄마
Congratulations, darling.
축하한다, 얘야
사랑한다
We love you, sweetheart.
너무 아름다워
You look beautiful.
-ls this new?
-Not now.
- 이거 새 거야?
- 이젠 아니지
-Who's this?
-I'm Father Karabasos.
- 이 사람 누구야?
- 카라바소스 신부요
He's Greek Orthodox.
그리스 정교회 신부셔
As are you.
너희들처럼
시작합시다
Let us begin.
Dearly beloved--
사랑하는 하객 여러분...
그건 내 대사예요!
That's my line!
I can take it from here. Thanks.
여기서부턴 제가하죠
사랑하는 하객 여러분
늦어서 죄송합니다
Dearly beloved,
I'm sorry I'm a little late.
옷차림 때문에
의아해 하시겠지만
You may be confused by this now...
...but you won't be
Memorial Day weekend, 2002.
오늘이 현충일 주말이라면
그렇지 않을 겁니다
신랑이 또 도망치기 전에
얼른 시작하죠
Let's get started before
the groom takes off again.
We are gathered here today...
오늘 여기에
...to join this man...
이 두 사람의
신성한 결혼식을 위해
다 모였습니다
...and this woman
in the bonds of holy matrimony.
I've known Monica and Chandler
for a long time, and I can't...
모니카와 챈들러를
오래 안 친구로 말하는데
...imagine two people more
perfect for each other.
두 사람만큼 서로에게
완벽한 사람은 없습니다
그리고 이제 제 메모를
탈의실에 두고 온 관계로
And now, as I've left my notes
in my dressing room...
...we shall proceed
to the vows. Monica?
혼인 서약으로 넘어가죠
모니카?
-He took off?
-Go on. Go on.
- 도망갔었다고?
- 어서 해
Chandler, for so long...
챈들러, 오랫동안
...I wondered if I would ever
find my prince.
내 왕자님이자 영혼의
동반자를 만날 수 있을지
My soul mate.
궁금해 했어
그러다 3년 전
누군가의 결혼식에서
Then three years ago,
at another wedding...
위로 받고자 찾은 친구에게
...I turned to a friend for comfort.
And instead, I found everything that
I'd been looking for my whole life.
내 일생동안 찾던
모든 것을 찾게 되었어
And now...
그리고 이제
...here we are...
이 자리에서
우리의 미래를
...with our future before us.
And I only want to spend it with you.
너와 함께 하고 싶어
My prince. My soul mate.
내 왕자님
내 영혼의 동반자
My friend.
내 친구
자기만 싫지 않다면
Unless you don't want to.
You go.
네 차례야
챈들러?
Chandler?
아냐, 됐어
No, that's okay.
I thought this would be the most
difficult thing I ever had to do.
결혼을 한다는 게 너무나
힘들다고 생각했어
그런데 네가 걸어오는 모습을
보고 그렇지 않다는 걸 알았어
But when I saw you walking down that
aisle, I realized it's simple.
널 사랑해
I love you.
어떤 놀랄 일이 있더라도
널 항상 사랑할 거야
Any surprises that come our way, it's
okay, because I will always love you.
You are the person I was meant
to spend the rest of my life with.
내 남은 여생을 같이
보낼 사람은 바로 너야
확인해 줄까?
You want to know if I'm sure?
신부에게 키스하세요
You may now kiss the bride.
I guess by the powers vested in me
by the State of New York...
뉴욕 주와 인터넷이
내게 준 권한으로
...and the lnternet guys...
...I now pronounce you
husband and wife.
두 사람을 부부로 선언하노라
잠깐, 서로를 받아들입니까?
Oh, wait. Do you take each other?
-I do.
- 네
그래야지!
Yeah, you do!
Rings?
반지
이런, 젠장, 좋아
Oh, crap.
반지 교환합시다
Let's do the rings.
We good? Yeah? Good?
다 됐어? 괜찮아?
Once again...
다시 한 번
두 사람을 부부로 선언하노라
...I pronounce you husband and wife.
또 키스해라
Now kiss her again.
사랑해
I love you.
And I know about the baby.
아기 얘기도 알아
-What baby?
-Our baby.
- 무슨 아기?
- 우리 아기
우리한테 아기가 있어?
We have a baby?
피비가 너 임신 테스트 봤대
Phoebe found your pregnancy test.
테스트한 적 없는데
I didn't take a pregnancy test.
그럼 누구지?
Then who did?
Look at them.
두 사람 좀 봐
And they're gonna have a baby.
곧 아기도 생기겠지